Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Publications 6317 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Publications
2011
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
Remember the Triangle Fire Coalition
6317 PUBS
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Publications.
7504503
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 16, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6317: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection 6317 MB: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Memorabilia 6317/001: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Remember the Triangle Fire Coalition Records 6317/001 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Remember the Triangle Fire Coalition Audio-Visual Materials 6317/015 P: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Anabella Lenzu Photographs 6317/001 G: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Remember the Triangle Fire Coalition Graphics 6317/001 MB: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Remember the Triangle Fire Coalition Memorabilia 6317/001 PUBS: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Remember the Triangle Fire Coalition Publications 6317/002 G: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Maribeth Whitehouse, IS 190 Class Graphics 6317/003: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Richard Strassberg 6317/004 PUBS: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Mark Tennyson Publications 6317/005: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection W4 New Music Booklets 6317/005 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection W4 New Music Audio-Visual Materials 6317/006 G: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection University of Iowa Labor Center Graphics 6317/007 P: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Denise J. Murphy Photographs 6317/008 PUBS: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection International Brotherhood of Teamsters, City Employees Union Local 237 Publications 6317/009: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Grey Art Gallery, New York University 6317/010: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Berkeley City College 6317/010 MB: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Berkeley City College Memorabilia 6317/010 P: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Berkeley City College Photographs 6317/011: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Working Women's History Project 6317/012 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection New York Society for Ethical Culture Audio-Visual Materials 6317/013 P: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Paul Margolis Photographs 6317/014: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection 59E59 Theaters 6317/015: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Anabella Lenzu Pamphlets 6317/016: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Theater for the New City 6317/016 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Theater for the New City Audio-Visual Materials 6317/017: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Bob Brener 6317/017 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Bob Brener Audio-Visual Materials 6317/018: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Manhattan Choral Ensemble 6317/018 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Manhattan Choral Ensemble Audio-Visual Materials 6317/019: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection West End Synagogue 6317/020 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Judson Memorial Church "From the Fire" Audio-Visual Materials 6317/021: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection New York State Museum Pamphlets 6317/022: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Anna Marie Landolfo Collection of Ephemera 6317/023: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection National Center for the Laity Newsletter 6317/024: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection International Labor Rights Forum Pamphlet 6317/025: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Kheel Center Collection of Newsclippings 6317/027(d): Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Memorial Design Competition Submissions (digital)
Clothing trade -- New York (State) -- New York -- History -- 20th century; Strikes and lockouts -- New York (State) -- New York -- History -- 20th century; Fires -- New York (State) -- New York -- History -- 20th century; Triangle Shirtwaist Company -- Fire, 1911
7504503
- Clara Lemlich Awards, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cooper Union Award Program, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- CUNY Grant Program, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Don't Mourn Organize, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Flyers (Box 1, Folder 5)
- From the Fire Program (Box 1, Folder 6)
- News and Views (Box 1, Folder 7)
- News Clippings (Box 1, Folder 8)
- I've Got Something to Say (Box 1, Folder 9)
- News Papers (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Triangle Fire Centennial Commemorative Program, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire: Why We Remember (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Various Event Programs (Box 1, Folder 13)
- West Fourth New Music Collective Concert Presents (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Mark Tennyson (Box 1, Folder 15)
- City Employees Union Local 237, Local 237 News Line (Box 1, Folder 16)